The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or common,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
In order to learn the mana method
and acquire the power they'll soon need,
Asta and the others train as hard as they can in the Heart Kingdom.
Gotcha this time!
The power to invalidate magic is second to nothing.
But you're too narrow-minded to use it to its full potential.
I'm not done!
Meanwhile, Dami seeks to improve in his own way.
Looks like they're all working hard to push past their limits.
So I guess I better up my game as well.
I'll be with you!
So,何度も 何度も 何度も 目の前の今を超えるさ
何度も 何度も 何度も 涙を希望に変えていこう
七色の日常を進め 永遠に光れ
永遠に光れ
Shine like a demon
天使と悪魔が交際してく
世界は矛盾だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで負ける夢はダサい
そう何度も何度も
夢の前の壁を越えるさ
何度も何度も
良さを未来に繋げよう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
You shine like a diamond
Lightning magic
Tengiolia
I've been sparring with this guy for days now and I still can't get a single hit in
It's fortunate that I opted to hold back you'd be in far worse shape if I hadn't
You've trained to your physical limit
obtain the rare power known as anti-magic
and forge friendships with capable allies
That's gotten you this far
However
It won't be enough to overcome the enemy that we're about to face
If you can't find a way to defeat me in one-on-one combat
You will fall to the Spade Kingdom Devil
One more round
Let's go
Perhaps it's that unwavering willpower that's allowed him to become this strong so quickly
It isn't just him though
All of the Clover Kingdom mages are growing quickly
Some have already developed new techniques here
Faster
I need to be faster
And stronger too
Hey Leopold
I should be able to do more
I know I should
Those were some really excellent moves
Good work
Nice use of the mana method too
You're a lot faster with it now
That said
Hmm
How to put this
Every now and again you seem to waver a bit when you're sparring with me
It feels like something's causing you to hesitate
Do you have any idea what that might be?
I think I know
I have an older brother and sister who I look up to
Their power is incredible
And it's been permanently seared into my eyes
I can't help but compare my own achievements to theirs
And when I do
I feel pathetic
Stand up
A lion should never look so pitiful
The stronger I get
The more out of reach they seem to become
It feels like no matter how hard I try
Or how far I get
They'll always be better
It's hot down here
Hey Siscolion good to see you
The name is Meryl Leona as you know
Did you come for a dip in the hot springs too?
Do your part and clear out some of the locals beforehand
Sheesh so you killed those magical beasts just to make sure they wouldn't interrupt your bath?
You are every bit as violent as I remember you being
Not like it was a big chore
I wouldn't even call that a warm up
Of course not
Tell you what though
If you need a warm up you can fight me
I see
Did you come all this way looking for me?
Yeah
I did
See when I was fighting that word devil
I was able to use a technique of yours
I think you call it monosome
But I don't have a good handle on how it works just yet
Something tells me I could get more use out of it
But if I did so I want to experiment a bit
Uh-huh
Couldn't you do that alone?
Well it's just that you're so experienced
I was hoping you'd be willing to show me the ropes
Fine
I was thinking that I should get some more training in
But be warned
Against me
You might just burn
Before you even get to try my technique
Oh boy
I'm not sure if she sees the difference between teaching me and killing me
Hey on second thought
I think I'll just go
That's probably not gonna fly is it
You're the one who chose to bring fresh meat into a lion's den
Well I guess it's best for you to come at me with some murderous intent
How else am I supposed to push past my limits
Very well
I'll warn you to a crisp
Urgh
U
A Yeaah
Urgh
u
at least. Exactly how long do you intend to struggle against me? Shall we fight until
you wear yourself out? Crap, what do I do? I can't get anywhere near this guy, so how
am I supposed to land a hit? Let's talk about your anti-magic. It's essentially the opposite
of magic, but opposites tend to share certain fundamentals. Both are forms of intangible
power. This could mean that they could be wielded in similar ways. The first step
of the mana method is to feel the mana flowing around you, so perhaps you should try something
similar. Right. I need to feel the flow of anti-magic.
She's faster than I can track. This all you got? Think you can dodge your way to victory?
How the hell is she this fast? No worries. If it's thanks to her monosone, then I should
be able to match her. Too slow! You want to see what monosone can do? I'll show you!
Well, this isn't good.
This place is way too hot. What was I thinking, fighting a monosone expert in a place like
this? Hey, I thought cats like to play with their food. Slow down, you furball.
Huh! I see no point in toying with weak prey. Why don't you try struggling more?
If this was a contest of speed alone, I'd probably lose.
Dark magic. Dark cloak, black blade!
Black divider!
You enlarged your blade to extend your rage. Not a bad idea, but you're still far too slow.
Even if I can sense him with my key, I can't keep up.
I'm using the mana method to enhance my speed, which makes avoiding you a simple task.
The Heart Kingdom teams with natural mana, and the mages here make regular use of it. For those of us who
master the mana method, this power source may as well be unlimited. Which means that as long as I can keep avoiding
your attacks, I can fight indefinitely without needing to tap into my own mana.
I get it. So if I keep burning through my anti-magic, I'm sure it'll lose.
You call that an attack? Come on! This is pathetic!
Why wait for the devil to end you? I can do your last rites here and now if you'd like.
Thing is, I already owe you so much for helping out with my training.
So thanks for the offer, but I'll pass.
Looks like step one's gonna be figuring out that trick where she walks on thin air.
Once I've learned that, I can enter the ring.
Come on. You need to come up with an attack that he can't dodge.
Something with the range to reach him and the speed to catch him.
I've already seen the powers of the Demon Slayer sword and the Demon Destroyer sword.
I assume that this sword is unique as well?
Right. The Demon Dweller sword. It probably has powers that I haven't drawn out yet.
That reminds me. Right after I found this sword, I channeled Noelle's mana with it.
Not sure, but there's a chance I can do the same thing with my own anti-magic.
Interesting. I take it you've had an epiphany.
Please let me have another try!
If that's what you want, I won't hold back as much this time.
If you manage to land a single hit on me, then I'll declare you victorious.
To be honest, I wish you'd just go all out!
If you won't move, I'll bring the fight to you!
You cannot kick the air.
Just as lions toss their young off cliffs to test them, I have absolutely no problem hurling you into the lava!
Are you really chasing me right now?
Sucks to admit, but Scolion's right. If I let myself lose here...
What chance would I have against that devil?
Ah, nice.
Looks like I can finally fight you on equal ground.
Equal ground? We're floating above lava, fool!
You get the point! I'm saying it's an even fight now!
Ha! When it comes to mana zone, you're just a baby learning to walk!
I need to figure out how to deal with those fists of hers.
All right, Asta. It's just like when you borrowed Noelle's mana.
I just need to infuse the Demon Dweller's sword with my anti-magic.
In accordance with your requests that I stop holding back, I will now show you my true power.
I just need to keep increasing my speed with mana zone, and stop her from throwing out any new spells!
You're not bad! You've developed a rudimentary grasp of how to use mana zone!
Which means I can stop holding back now!
Do you seriously think you were holding back before? No way!
This gift is to thank you for the good time! Do your best not to let it kill you!
Not sure I can stop all that. Then again, I have to!
No point in asking if I can! I have to, so I will!
Right here, right now! I'll push past my limit!
Mana zone, dark magic, black hole!
Okay, now...
Is he... nullifying my mana?
Dark magic, dark cloak, blightless, slash!
Quite impressive...
Impressive.
Way to go, V! I actually got a hit in!
This is getting interesting.
Once I've burnt you to cinders, my bath will be that much more enjoyable.
Got the gist of it, so I'm leaving.
Don't be coy, or are you just afraid?
Terrified. I'll catch you later!
Well, that's disappointing.
It's time we shared our progress. Please report.
Rill and Charmy are doing great.
They both took to the Mono Method faster than expected.
They're brilliant, if a little unusual.
The most I can do for them now is prepare their meals
and bring out their potential with the occasional word of advice.
Mm-hmm.
Charlotte and Mimosa have come a super long way.
They seemed confused at first, but then something went calick in their heads, you know?
Our students have grown, too.
I suspect they've grown faster than any of yours.
Although, when someone's being instructed by the Queen of the Heart Kingdom
and the Great Water Spirit herself, I suppose that's only to be expected.
I can tell you're proud of them.
Tell me, Smearath, how has Venril been coming along?
For the time being, we must let the wind guide us
and trust it to nurture the storm that grows within him.
You have an awfully hard time getting to the point, don't you?
Did someone say something?
I couldn't quite make it out over the whispers of the wind.
Don't fight, you two.
Floga, how goes it?
Not bad.
Leo's a talented mage, but he's plagued by self-doubt.
I think you'll get better results if you try to focus on your strengths.
My strengths?
Like what?
You didn't get this far on talent.
You did it with patience and determination.
Your power grows as your technique improves, with every day of practice.
You're the kind of person who has the strength to endure anything.
I mean, you're you, right?
The strength to endure anything.
I want to draw out potential he hasn't realized yet.
At least that's my idea.
We'll see how it goes.
Yes.
Well, I'm sure you'll get through to him.
And what about Asta?
Asta's anti-magic is uniquely potent.
We'll need it to defeat this devil.
As for Asta's progress, he's becoming stronger in his own way.
Unfortunately, time is running short now.
Please put everything you have into this training.
Yes, ma'am.
Let us join together to beat the Spade Kingdom, and the devil lurking within it.
There are so many.
Looks like they're almost ready to start the invasion.
If we're going to make our move, we need to be fast.
Look there.
How fortunate.
Through your labors, you people will get to contribute to the Spade Kingdom's prosperity.
Where are they making us go now?
We have to stay quiet.
Come on, buddy.
You're almost there.
Don't, Ralph.
There are too many of them.
I know, but still.
We've reached the strong magic region.
It's unlikely that all of us will make it across.
But remember, only one of us needs to reach the Clover Kingdom.
As long as one of us makes it, there's hope.
Hang on to that hope no matter what happens.
Let's go!
Look at that.
We've found ourselves a pack of stray rebels.
Your friend ratted you out, but that isn't too surprising.
Not with a beloved child's life on the line.
Run for it!
If I bring your heads back to my superior, I'll get a promotion and a raise for sure.
Don't turn your back to me!
Ralph!
What are you?
I'm trusting you with our mana.
Use it well.
You're on your own now.
You have to pull through.
For him!
Our hopes go with you.
Finish the work your father started.
You won't escape us.
Go now!
I'll reach the Clover Kingdom, no matter what it takes.
Strong magic region is just past this cliff.
Can I really cross it?
Stop that.
Don't let their sacrifice go to waste.
Follow in your father's footsteps.
You can't give up.
There he is!
Get him!
I can't let them take me.
I'm the last hope.
For you now!
Did we hit him?
I couldn't tell.
But even if he's alive, that's a strong magic region. The environment will kill him before long.
And I don't know about you two, but I'd rather not chase him.
Yeah, he'll die soon.
Serves him right. Damn resistance. Let's go.
I don't like being this close to the strong magic region. Who knows what'll happen if we stay too long.
Heh. Nothing good.
You say this is the son of one of the Mage Defense Force's former commanders?
Yes. We interrogated one of the rebel conspirators we captured and learned that his name is Ralph. And sir, his name actually appears in a...
It matters not. Let this fly buzz around as he will. We'll swat him down if he decides to stand in the way of our grand design.
Tonsure Man
Walk on my way
Haleに転んで傷ついて
気付けば誰ももうどこにもいない
歪んだ世界に魔法の言葉で
光が射すなら飛びつくんだろう
今目の前に残るのは希望か
掴みかけた若干な幸福が
まだ消せない誓い叫んでる
忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって
全然届かなくても
信じる君は赤い手前を向いている
だから枯れないように柄がって
描いた夢また歩き出せる
きっと僕を呼ぶ声だ
次回は Black Cloverの第1章をご覧ください
Who am I you ask
I guess I wouldn't mind sharing a little
Next time on Black Clover
Page 157
Five Leaf Clover
Within the Clover's fifth leaf
There lives a devil